---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=4e88ae36e0b5fa07660130fcd16e514c; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        breed of dog was Marley in the film &quot;Marley &amp; Me&quot; (2008)?","correct_answer":"Labrador
        Retriever","incorrect_answers":["Golden Retriever","Dalmatian","Shiba Inu"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who wrote and directed
        the 1986 film &#039;Platoon&#039;?","correct_answer":"Oliver Stone","incorrect_answers":["Francis
        Ford Coppola","Stanley Kubrick","Michael Cimino"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Cartoon & Animations","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        was the first Disney movie to use CGI?","correct_answer":"The Black Cauldron","incorrect_answers":["Tron","Toy
        Story","Fantasia"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        the show &quot;Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann&quot; what is the name of the character
        who force everyone to live underground?","correct_answer":"Lordgenome","incorrect_answers":["Kingloname","Lord
        Genome","King Loname"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In
        most traditions, who was the wife of Zeus?","correct_answer":"Hera","incorrect_answers":["Aphrodite","Athena","Hestia"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon,
        Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"BMW
        M GmbH is a subsidiary of BMW AG that focuses on car performance.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the name of Manchester United&#039;s home stadium?","correct_answer":"Old
        Trafford","incorrect_answers":["Anfield","City of Manchester Stadium","St
        James Park"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the profession of Elon Musk&#039;s mom, Maye Musk?","correct_answer":"Model","incorrect_answers":["Professor","Biologist","Musician"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the largest country in the world ?","correct_answer":"Russian Federation","incorrect_answers":["China","Canada","Brazil"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
